傑姬·夏普
Jackie Sharp.
缺乏經驗
泰瑞·烏麥克
Terry Womack.
唯唯諾諾
鮑勃·博奇
Bob Birch.
不問時事
沃克總統面對著一個千瘡百孔的國會
President Walker has surrounded himself with a broken Congress.
他甚至還提拔國會的人進白宮
He even brought one of them into the White House.
他們整垮了經濟
Now, they've broken the economy
還與中國起了爭端
and put us on a collision course with China.
趁來得及  快阻止他們
Put a stop to them before it's too late.
停下
廢物
在中期選舉中表明立場
Send a message at the midterms.
讓美國變得更好
Let's start fixing the country.
為美國投票
由美國進步之友贊助播出
Paid for by Friends of a Better America.
兩千五百萬  憑空變出來的
Twenty-five million? Out of thin air?
-初步估計是這樣    -錢是哪來的
- That's our estimate.   - Where is the money coming from?
-超級政治行動委員會    -這廣告是攻擊具體事件的
- Super PACs.   - These are issue-based attack ads.
錢是誰給的
So who's giving to them?
得等這季財報才能確定來源
We can't trace the money until this quarter's filings come in.
中期選舉栽了  下次大選也泡湯了
We get killed in the midterms, we can kiss 2016 goodbye.
共和黨就會佔據國會多數席位和白宮
You can deal with the republican majority and a Republican president.
我們和民主黨議會競選委員會在努力還擊
We're trying to counter with D-trip.
憑空變出兩千五百萬嗎
Make 25 million appear out of nowhere?
-至少能造出點聲勢    -那不夠
- We can make a dent.   - Dents don't cut it.
不管款籌得多快
Well, no matter how fast we ramp up fundraising,
都補不上缺口
we can't close the gap.
得切斷他們的資金來源
We have to stop their money flow.
怎麼切
I want to know how.
找到源頭  釜底抽薪
Locate the source and then cut off the tap.
憑空出現這麼多錢
With this sorta influx you can be sure that
肯定有人違規了
somebody's not playing by the rules,
但找不到源頭就沒法告狀
but we can't whistle-blow until we find the source.
那就去找  而且趕快找到
Then find it. And you sure as hell better find it soon.
我在構思還擊的對策
In the meantime, I've been working on a proposal to counter the attacks.
協調全國上下發出訊息
A coordinated national messaging effort.
明天晚些時候發給你們
I'll be sending all of you copies later today.
我們要考慮一切辦法
Well, we should be open to every idea.
好了  去幹活兒吧
Now, go. Get to work.
弗蘭克
Frank.
你本該代表我控制國會
You were supposed to steer Congress on my behalf.
我心情無比焦慮
No one is as concerned as me.
真應該把你留在國會
I shoulda kept you in the house,
向雷蒙德最初說的那樣
like Raymond suggested from day one.
可你分心去摻和參議院  國情諮文
But you've been distracted by the Senate, State of the Union,
還干預外交
meddling with foreign diplomacy.
-是你要我去談判的    -我知道我做了什麼
- You asked me to negotiate--   - I know what I've done.
我也知道後果
And I know where it's gotten us.
先生  攻擊我們的廣告不是因為
Sir, the attack ads are not a result of anything--
你慌慌忙忙地到處撲火  而不是防止失火
You're scrambling from fire to fire instead of preventing them.
我不是聯邦選舉委員會  不能變魔...
I'm not the FEC, I can't wave a wand--
別就知道找藉口  弗蘭克  你不止這點本事
Give me more than excuses, Frank! You're better than that!
沒準就是這點
Or maybe you're not.
你要是想找個沙袋撒氣
If you need a punching bag,
那我就站在這兒讓你出氣
I will stand here and take the punches,
自我上任以來
as I have done time and time again,
我一次次做你的沙袋
since I swore my oath.
可我更想照你的吩咐  回去工作
But I would much rather get back to work, as you've asked me to do.
你太過分了  弗蘭克
You are out of line, Frank.
不出拳就放我走吧  總統先生
Dismiss me or keep swinging, Mr. President.
你走吧
You're dismissed.
謝謝  先生
Thank you, sir.
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用於任何商業盈利行為
翻譯 somehacker   小飯   宅女之後   章魚X   某豚
翻譯 艾瑞卡   香茗小焙   衛老哥   癢癢   葉某人
藍光版調整  timhal@HDWinG字幕組   後期 餓得慌
顧問 老杜   校對 草草   總監 草草
本字幕由YYETS翻譯 HDWinG字幕組修正 請勿去掉製作者資訊
《紙牌屋》
第二季  第七集
丹·拉尼根轉投那邊了
Dan Lanagin switched teams.
這不可能啊
That doesn't make any sense.
共和黨的大捐助人都沒什麼異常
I couldn't find any anomalies among big Republican donors,
於是我查了民主黨的
so I checked our own.
拉尼根這季一分都沒捐
Lanagin hasn't given a dime this quarter.
是啊  沒捐和資助共和黨不一樣
Yeah, but not giving isn't the same as giving to the Republicans.
他賭場的賬目  安永事務所做的
His casino's accounts. Ernst and Young.
捐了一千八百萬  還不是給我們
Eighteen million for donations, and they're not going to us.
你怎麼弄到的
How did you get your hands on those?
我有朋友  所以你才找我幫忙
I've got friends. That's why you solicit my services.
那廣告花了大約兩千五百萬
The estimate for the ad buys was 25 million.
賬目只到6月30日
Those accounts are up to date as of June 30th.
那之後應該還捐款了
They could have made more donations since then.
塔斯克
Tusk.
拉尼根的賭場在密蘇里
Lanagin's casino is in Missouri.
雷蒙德·塔斯克嗎
Raymond Tusk?
他對我和總統有不滿
He's got an axe to grind with me and with the president.
選舉委員會的檔案裡沒他的名字
I've never seen his name on any FEC filings.
他從不捐助政黨
He doesn't make political contributions.
所以才能進退自如
That's how he remains flexible.
你覺得他在想辦法籌集資金嗎
You think he's funneling the money somehow?
我不知道
I don't know.
你去堪薩斯城  去那家賭場
Get yourself to Kansas City. I want you in that casino.
-是  先生    -我會繼續查的
- Yes, sir.   - I'll keep digging.
接我太太的電話
Get me my wife.
-你從哪得到的菜譜    -我父親教我的
- Where'd you get the recipe?   - My father taught me.
-你跟你爸爸很親密嗎    -不
- You and your dad were close?   - Nah.
烹飪肋排是那混蛋唯一能做好的事
Cooking ribs was the only thing that motherfucker did right.
-這話不能上報紙吧    -我有辦法
- I guess you can't print that.   - I have ways.
真的會上報紙嗎
This really gonna be in the paper?
至少能上波士頓的報紙
At least in Boston, yeah.
我怎麼覺得沒人會在意
Don't see why anybody would care.
這是關於個人喜好
Well, it's a personal interest story.
那麼多餐廳  美國副總統卻偏偏喜歡這裡
The vice president of the United States comes here, of all places.
-你是說這破地方嗎    -我可沒這麼說
- You mean this shithole?   - That's not what I said.
沒關係
It's OK.
又不是泰姬陵
It's not the Taj Mahal.
他從什麼時候開始來這裡
How long has he been coming?
大概有20年了吧
About 20 years now.
-他是個好人  弗蘭克    -你還叫他弗蘭克嗎
- He's a good man, Frank.   - You still call him Frank?
在這裡  我才是總統
Hey, in this joint, I'm the president,
是副總統  也是國會
the vice president and the Congress.
他只是一名顧客  忠實的顧客
He just another customer. A loyal one.
所以他才喜歡這裡嗎
You think that's why he likes it here?
因為你像對待普通人那樣對待他
'Cause you treat him like a regular person?
也許吧  不過主要還是因為這肋排
Maybe. Mostly it's the fuckin' ribs, though.
如果失業率上升至20%以上
Now, if unemployment goes up more than two-tenths,
我希望美聯儲考慮...
I want the Fed to consider...
總統先生
這個沙袋不像我話那麼多
來點什麼嗎  親愛的
Get you something, hon.
請給我青檸蘇打水
Club soda with lime, please?
-就這樣嗎    -對
- That's it?   - Yeah.
-不要吃的嗎    -不用  就這樣
- Nothing to eat?   - No. That's it.
你要是在戒酒  在這地方待著可挺受煎熬
Tough spot to hang out if you're in the program.
-你怎麼知道    -酒鬼眼裡分外明
- How'd you know?   - Takes one to know one, right?
-你多久了    -剛過一年  你呢
- How long?   - Little over a year. You?
就要15年了
Going on 15.
賽馬贏錢了嗎
Any luck with the ponies?
沒有  還沒
None. Not yet.
選個數字  1到12
Pick a number. One through twelve.
Nine.
名聲大噪
Hot Fuss.
聽起來不錯
Sounds about right.
蘇打水馬上來  親愛的  配青檸
Club soda coming up, darling. With lime.
過去兩小時他都沒有動
Hasn't moved the last two hours.
也沒跟任何人說話嗎
And he hasn't spoken to anybody?
一直在賭
Just been betting on the races.
要我們帶他進來嗎
You want us to bring him in?
不  那是副總統的幕僚長
No. That's the vice president's chief of staff.
真的嗎
Really?
別引發混亂  盯住他就行
We don't want to make a scene. Just keep an eye on him.
告訴我他幹了什麼  去了哪裡  跟誰說過話
Let me know what he does, where he goes, and who he talks to.
明白  拉尼根先生
You got it, Mr. Lanagin.
你真該看看他們的表情
You should've seen their faces.
他們徹底糊塗了
They didn't know what to think.
特別是我讓他們扶住沙袋時
Especially when I made 'em hold the bag.
你試過了嗎
You tried it out?
那是當然
I sure as hell did.
很抱歉我那麼衝你發脾氣  弗蘭克
I'm sorry I lashed out at you, Frank.
不  是我失禮了  有失妥當
No. I was disrespectful, and that was uncalled for.
我的情緒最近總有些失控
My temper's gotten away from me these days.
我有時需要被人吼一吼  清醒過來
I need to be jolted back into reality sometimes.
你是出於好意
It was a -- a kind gesture.
就是消遣罷了
Oh, just some good old fun.
特莉莎說我們這周要一起吃晚飯
Tricia tells me we're having dinner later this week.
是的  克萊爾也這樣跟我說
Yes. Claire tells me the same.
能離開這裡幾小時也不錯
Well, it'll be good to get out of this place for a few hours.
這幅畫從肯尼迪時期就掛在這裡了
It's been here since Kennedy.
是他出生那年畫的
It was painted the same year he was born.
描繪的好像是一戰的慶祝遊行
It depicts, I think, a World War I parade.
每一幅畫我都該瞭解一下
Oh, I should know every painting.
你似乎懂不少呢  至少瞭解這幅
Well, you seem to know quite a lot, at least about this one.
我想趁現在有機會  好好研究一下
Oh, I try to soak it all in while I can.
所有的歷史
All the history.
癡迷於歷史的總統
Presidents who obsess over history
癡迷於他們在歷史中的地位
obsess about their place in it,
而不是如何創造歷史
instead of forging it.
誰說的
Who said that?
我  就在剛才
I did. Just now.
白宮  一整天都熙熙攘攘
Ah, the White House. All day long it's buzzing,
這個時候卻又如此冷清
and at this hour it's so desolate.
做總統是件偉大而珍貴的事情
The presidency is a great and precious thing.
而代價就是孤獨
Loneliness is the price.
做個假設
Let's assume
如果杜魯門總統就是坐在這其中一張椅子上
in one of these chairs, staring at this wall,
盯著牆  決定投放核彈
is where Truman decided to drop the bomb.
看看我們會不會有什麼感覺
And see if we feel anything.
沒感覺  你呢
Nothing. You?
沒有
No.
抱歉  這兒很亂
Sorry, it's a mess.
不用為我收拾
You don't have to clean up for me.
當然要
Yes, I do.
我不想你看到這個
Wouldn’t want you seeing these.
我昨晚穿著這個
I wore 'em last night.
你喜歡這個  還是我現在這身
You like these or you want the ones I'm wearing now?
你在賭場工作多久了
How long you been working in the casino?
很久了
Too long.
那你一定見多識廣
Bet you've seen a lot.
當然  我什麼都見過
Oh, yeah. I've seen everything.
我得走了  要開早會
I should get going. Got an early meeting.
好
Okay.
你想我留下來嗎
Do you want me to stay?
我沒想在這兒過夜
I wasn't planning on sleeping here.
又是一次一夜情嗎
So, uh, another one-night stand then, huh?
有問題嗎
Is that okay?
不是我的風格
Not really my thing.
得了吧  你肯定是老手了
Come on. You must play the field.
不  我不是
No, I don't.
但你很會調情啊
But you are such a flirt.
我的確會調情
I flirt, yes.
但我只跟喜歡的人上床
But I only sleep with someone if I'm into them.
而且我喜歡留下過夜
And I prefer to stick around.
雷米·丹頓  專情男子
Remy Danton, serial monogamist.
你是在開玩笑嗎
This a joke?
抱歉  我不是...抱歉
I'm sorry. I didn't, uh... sorry.
如果你不是認真的  就不會有下一次了
This doesn't happen again unless it's leading somewhere.
我對自己想要的東西都很直接
I'm upfront about what I want, in all things.
不僅僅是在政治上
Not just politics.
每年三四次  會有十幾個有錢的中國人來
Three or four times a year they fly in about a dozen Chinese guys.
專門來燒錢
Money to burn.
他們把賭場一整層預留給他們
They got a whole floor of the casino reserved just for them.
據說能輸掉幾百萬
Word is they throw away millions.
這說明不了什麼
Well, that doesn't necessarily mean anything.
中國人都愛賭博  特別是富人
The Chinese love to gamble. Especially the rich ones.
沒錯  他們會去維加斯
Yeah, in Vegas.
這是密蘇里  遠多了
This is Missouri. It's a much longer flight.
我想要知道
I want to find out --
I want to find out
這些人是從哪飛過來的
where these planes are coming from.
我們認識聯邦航空管理局的人嗎
Who do we know in the FAA?
我不認識  但道爾認識  我讓他去打探了
I don't know anyone. But Doyle does. I already got him on it.
有訊息就通知你
I'll text you when I hear back from Doyle.
我得走了
I gotta go.
要走了嗎
You leaving?
是的  謝謝讓我度過美好的一晚
Yeah. Thanks for last night.
-我很開心    -不  才沒有
- I had fun.   - No, you didn't.
你在想著別人
You were thinking of somebody else.
這是我十年戒酒紀念章
I got that one after ten years.
希望能給你帶來好運
Hope it brings you some luck.
法案由艾琳·布魯克斯發起
Elaine Brooks will be sponsoring
第一夫人已經認同了初稿
and the First Lady has approved the early draft.
傑姬  看看那板子
Jackie, take a look at the board.
除了你  想想還有誰能做聯署人
Get a sense of who might cosponsor, besides yourself.
當然  我們肯定能拉來不少重量級人物
Absolutely. I'm sure we can lock down a lot of heavyweights.
洛莉和我會處理這事
Lorrie and I will get right on it.
我們該想想媒體計劃
We should talk about a media plan.
-現在還太早了    -難道不該宣傳嗎
- It's premature for that.   - Don't we want to get this out,
儘早開始博取支援
start building support as soon as possible?
-做活動和採訪    -我只想看到最佳成效
- Events, interviews?   - I want what's most effective.
媒體大肆宣揚不好
A media blitz is the wrong way to go.
應該始終只用一個引子
You want a single long lead
與法案出臺同步  要有檔次
that coincides with the introduction of the bill. Something classy.
-但要廣泛支援才能...    -大肆宣傳
- But you want broad support, to hit--   - A blanket strategy will
能博取支援  但也可能招致批評
galvanize as many detractors as supporters.
如果我們把理念包裝得當...
Not if the message is framed in such way--
我們得先獲取目標群體的認同  然後...
We want a key demographic to get on board, and then--
-請讓我說完    -然後慢慢積累
- Let me finish, please.   - Then we let it percolate.
我建議找《紐約時代雜誌》的馬特·貝
I suggest Matt Bai, The New York Times Magazine.
我喜歡這想法  非常喜歡
I like that idea. I like it very much.
我也是  你能和馬特聯繫嗎
So do I. Can you speak to Matt?
先別定下來  接觸一下看看情況
No promises. Just test the waters.
我願意去找他談
I'm happy to do that.
我和馬特關係不錯  我給他打個電話
I've got a good relationship with Matt. I'll call him.
很好  賽斯  有進展隨時通知我
Great. Seth, you keep me posted,
這周晚些時候再碰個頭
and let's all get together later this week.
多謝了  傑姬
Thanks, Jackie.
你讀一下法案  給我寫份摘要
I want you to read the bill and write me a summary.
我們談過之前  絕不要跟任何人透露一個字
Do not under any circumstances share it with anyone until we've spoken.
你不先過一遍議員名單嗎
You don't want to go over the board first, at least --
不  不急
No. Not yet.
關於墮胎查到了什麼
Anything on the abortion?
一無所獲  全都核實了
Nothing. It all checks out.
-完全確定嗎    -我方方面面都查了
- One hundred percent?   - I turned over every stone.
-安德伍德夫人說的是實話    -我需要猛料
- Mrs. Underwood was telling the truth.   - We need something.
時間拖得太久了
This is taking too long.
安德伍德夫婦都很小心
The Underwoods are careful.
如果真有醜聞  肯定藏得非常深
If they have skeletons, they're buried deep.
這不是"如果"的問題
Not a question of "If."
弗蘭克這樣的人肯定有醜聞
Somebody like Frank is gonna have skeletons.
那我會挖出來的
Then I'll find them.
你這邊一無所獲  我就沒法向上面交代
If you don't deliver, that means I don't deliver.
那不是我的風格
And I always deliver.
你給了我這個任務  而且期望我做好
You gave me an assignment with high expectations.
我不會讓你失望的  但也別指望一蹴而就
I will meet them. But it's not gonna happen overnight.
所以別跟我頤指氣使
So don't fuck with me.
我只是你僱來辦事的人  不是你的走狗
I'm a hired gun. Not one that you own.
只要你能達成目的就行
As long as you hit the target.
那你得幫我個忙
Then I need a favor.
康納·埃利斯
Connor Ellis?
他怎麼了
What about him?
沒他礙事的話我會擁有更多許可權
I'll have more access if he isn't around.
你能不能找個美差把他引走
Arrange a cushy job offer for him somewhere?
私企還是政府部門
Private or public sector?
私企的
Private.
收入豐厚
Lots of money.
讓他難以拒絕
Something he can't turn down.
我想想辦法
I'll see what I can do.
給  先付一半
Here, this is half.
等我完成任務時再付我錢吧
You can pay me when I've gotten you what you want.
我從不事做一半  錢也拿一半
I don't take half pay for a job half done.
這是個很有趣的提案
It's an interesting proposal.
我們缺的就是一個統一的主題
What we're missing is a unified theme.
如果能協調全國廣告投入  組織跨黨派活動
If we coordinate on national ad-buys, organize crossover events,
開發捐款應用  應該能收效頗豐...
develop fund-raising apps, I think it would go a long way...
也許吧  但我覺得總統不太可能同意
Maybe, but I doubt the leadership will go for it.
所以我希望你能支援  我安排了一次會議
Which is why I'd like your support. I set up a meeting.
你要是能來  並且支援我的立場
If you came, and you supported my position...
我估計他們最終會說
I just think they're gonna end up saying
不能為全國範圍的策略燒錢
we can't be thinning out our funds on a national strategy.
必須要落到實處  爭取選票
This is about fieldwork, getting out the vote.
那好  但至少該考慮一下吧
Right, but isn't it worth at least some consideration?
你瞭解我的  琳達  我喜歡大膽的點子
Well, you know me, Linda, I mean, I'm all for bold ideas.
道·斯坦普  飛機是我們那位中國朋友的公司的
但博奇和烏麥克  他們太守舊了
But Birch and Womack, why, they're... set in their ways.
弗·安德伍德  來過多少次
我覺得他們不太可能...
I doubt very seriously that...
道·斯坦普  2005年起來堪薩斯城38次
聽著  弗蘭克  我只想要你
Listen, Frank, all I'm asking is that
跟他們唱反調
you play devil's advocate with them.
對不起  給我點時間  我有點要緊事
Sorry, excuse me for a moment. This is important.
這事我很在乎的  弗蘭克
I don't want to short-shrift this, Frank.
弗·安德伍德  我要你去問他本人
我知道  先讓我發完這條簡訊
No, I know, but I just have to send this text.
我也不是閒人
I am busy too.
弗·安德伍德  當著面他不好撒謊
道·斯坦普  已經買票了
美國航空
-請給我訂靠過道的座位    -好的
- Make sure that's an aisle seat.   - Of course.
我覺著你根本不重視這事
I don't feel as if you're taking this very seriously.
琳達  我向你道歉  對不起
Linda, I apologize. I am sorry.
你說得沒錯  我沒有敷衍你的意思
You are absolutely right, I did not mean to sound curt.
你是對的  這是很重要
And you are right, this is important.
咱倆這就好好談談你的提案
You and I should go through your proposal
仔細推敲每一個細節
and discuss it right down to the last detail.
我沒想讓你逐字逐句地看
I am not asking you to go through it page by page,
只要幫忙讓他們願意認真考慮就行
just to help me initiate some meaningful dialogue.
-我當然會幫你了  琳達    -多謝你
- You can count on my help, Linda.   - Thank you.
-我會讓排程員聯繫你這邊    -好的  琳達
- I will have my scheduler reach out to yours.   - Thank you, Linda.
請接內線
Get me a secure line, please.
副總統來電
The vice president is on the line.
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President.
通常我會無視你的來電  但我今天心情不錯
Normally, I would ignore your call, but I am in a good mood today.
你都沒法破壞
Not even you could ruin it.
你是不是在向共和黨捐款
Are you funneling money to the Republicans?
你到底在說什麼
What on earth are you talking about?
給了共和黨超級政治行動委員會大概兩千萬
About 20 million in GOP Super PACs.
你知道我從不給政黨捐款
Now you know I never make political contributions.
很容易讓我的投資者不高興
That's the fastest way to upset my investors.
我知道錢的來路 是密蘇里的一家賭場
I know the money is coming from a casino in Missouri
我還知道是馮給的
and I know it's from Feng.
馮先生和我只合作過一次
Mr. Feng and I have one co-venture together,
而且和賭博毫無關係
and it has nothing to do with gambling.
他的一架私人飛機定期飛往拉尼根的賭場
A plane that he owns flies to Lanagin's casino on a regular basis.
他私人時間做什麼  與我無關
What he does on his own time is no business of mine.
你是想給領導層添亂嗎
Are you trying to create chaos in the ranks?
共和黨沒有我的幫助似乎也做到了
The Republicans appear to be doing a fine job of that without my help.
你不會得逞的  雷蒙德
Well, it's not gonna work, Raymond.
這只會讓民主黨更團結  而不是分裂
It'll bind the democrats together, not pull us apart.
要我猜的話  過去十年裡讓民主黨團結的
What has bound them together the past decade has been
是資助你們成為多數黨的捐助
the means to achieve a majority, if I had to guess...
是他用錢鑄就了國會
He stacked Congress.
鑄就了我任黨鞭的多數黨
The majority I whipped.
原來一直是你在操縱  雷蒙德
So it's been you, Raymond, all along,
拉尼根的錢流向我們的時候也是
even when Lanagin's money was coming to us.
你總在做我已經否認的假設
You keep making assumptions that I have denied.
等季度報告一出來
Once the quarterly filings come out,
有電腦的人都會明白是怎麼回事
anybody with a laptop is gonna see what's going on.
那是在九月底
The end of September.
還早著呢  但我很期待看到那些報告
That's a long way off. But I look forward to seeing the reports.
在中期選舉兩週前
Should make for some very interesting reading
肯定是很有趣的讀物
two weeks before the midterms.
你別想靠恐嚇回到決策桌上  雷蒙德
You cannot bully your way back to the table, Raymond,
你也休想收買國會
just as you cannot buy the keys to Congress.
祝你成功維持眾議院多數席位
Best of luck keeping your majority in the House.
我知道那對你來說意義重大
I know how much it means to you.
有錢給你用的時候  大家都不會多想
When the money's coming your way, you don't ask any questions.
但這下清楚了  拉尼根不過是個幌子
But now it's clear. Lanagin's never been anything but a front.
我要告訴總統嗎  不
Do I tell the president? No.
他會想我之前怎麼不知道
He'll wonder why I didn't know,
那我就顯得訊息不靈了
which makes me look uninformed,
或者他會責備傳話的人  把他也捲進去
or he'll blame the messenger for involving him,
那就顯得我太大意了
which makes me look careless.
我知道這是個陷阱  我得守住這個祕密
I know it's a trap. I must keep this to myself.
他問你代表誰進行購買
He wants to know who you are buying on behalf of.
一家名叫水星資本的對沖基金  還沒上市
It's a hedge fund named Mercury Capital. It's unlisted.
他們需要主要投資者的名字
They need the names of the principal investors.
告訴他們我得保護他們的身份
Tell him I have to protect identities.
代理人需要更多資訊  他要完整的投資人名單
The broker needs more. He wants a full investor list.
跟他說
Say, um...
就說主要投資者和白宮聯繫密切
Say that the principal investor has strong ties to the White House.
他們問你是不是代表克雷頓-維斯特
And they want to know if you represent Clayton West.
克雷頓-維斯特嗎
Clayton West?
搜索  克雷頓-維斯特
雷蒙德·斯塔克
-他還在等    -稍候
- He's waiting.   - One second.
搜索  馮山德  雷蒙德·塔斯克
上面寫了些什麼
What does it say?
是關於一家中國的稀土精煉廠
It's about a refinery in China for rare earth elements.
跟他說是  告訴他主要投資者是雷蒙德·塔斯克
Tell him yes. Tell him the principal investor is Raymond Tusk.
我是道格·斯坦普
This is Doug Stamper...
-我們該用什麼招待沃剋夫婦    -氰化物
- What should we serve the Walkers?   - Cyanide.
用來做甜點好了  主餐呢
Saving that for dessert. What about a main course?
哪種肉  或是蔬菜
Meat of some sort? Vegetables?
我實在不太擅長這方面
I mean, this isn't really my area of expertise.
我在想  不如找弗萊迪來
I was thinking, what about Freddy?
-吃肋排嗎    -這樣會不會太唐突
- Ribs?   - Or is that gauche?
不會  我喜歡這主意
No. I like the idea.
我們可以用高檔瓷器  精緻配菜
Well, we can do the nice china, gourmet sides,
但我覺得肋排更有人情味
but I think the ribs make it more personal.
我去打電話
I'll make the call.
-你正在等的這通電話有訊息嗎    -還沒有
- Any word on the call you're expecting?   - Not yet.
我想他的航班應該還沒到
I don't think he's landed.
你還真搭起來了啊
This is really coming along, isn't it?
你覺得小孩子氣
You think it's childish.
總比打遊戲好
I think it's better than video games.
把我的五千美金支票帶來了嗎
Do you have my check for $5,000?
等我漲工資了再說吧
Next time when I get a raise.
在賭場運氣不好嗎
Bad luck at the casino?
塔斯克知道我在這兒
So Tusk knows I'm here.
-丹尼爾·拉尼根知道    -塔斯克跟這事有關嗎
- Daniel Lanagin knows you're here.   - Is Tusk involved?
我為什麼要承認
Why would I admit that?
塔斯克和你有生意來往
Tusk is in business with you.
你在給拉尼根匯錢
You're sending money to Lanagin.
拉尼根的賭場又歸塔斯克管
Lanagin's casino is in Tusk's backyard.
你大老遠飛來
You didn't fly halfway around the
不會就是為了證實猜測吧
world just to confirm suspicions.
告訴我你想要什麼
Tell me what you want.
我們想中止資金繼續流向共和黨
We want the money to stop flowing to the Republicans.
我有什麼好處
And what do I receive?
我說了我們想要的  現在到你了
I've told you what we want. Now it's your turn.
好讓你再次誤導我嗎
Ah, so you can mislead me again.
形勢變了  誤導你對我們沒有好處
Things have changed. We have nothing to gain by misleading you.
你覺得我的花園如何
What do you think of my garden?
非常漂亮
It's very beautiful.
只知道談生意  就會忘記欣賞美景
When you only talk business, you stop appreciating beauty.
我沒什麼時間賞景
I don't have much time for beauty.
真可惜
That's a shame.
為了讓你們這些老闆有閒暇賞景
For people like you to smell the flowers,
我們這些手下得去除雜草
some of us have to pull the weeds.
-打算什麼時候走    -還沒買回程票
- When do you plan on leaving?   - I haven't bought my return ticket yet.
很好
Good.
我需要考慮一晚
I'd like to think on this for a night.
我想你一定累壞了
And I'm sure you must be exhausted.
可否賞臉在這兒做客
Would you do me the honor of being my guest?
-非常感謝    -很好  你能休息一下了
- I'd be very grateful.   - Excellent. You can get some rest.
你要是喜歡
And if you like,
這裡還有很多美的事物可以享受
there are many beautiful things to enjoy here.
請
Please.
道·斯坦普  見面了  馮山德在拖延
弗·安德伍德  沒得到答覆絕不離開
道·斯坦普  對了  我們聖路易斯和堪薩斯的朋友知道我在這兒
弗·安德伍德  帶那位印第安朋友來華盛頓  我要當面會會他
道·斯坦普  這就和堪薩斯聯繫
弗·安德伍德  越快越好
先生  格雷森先生到了
Sir, Mr. Grayson is here.
賽斯
Seth.
你上任以來我們還一直沒機會
You and I haven't really properly had the chance to sit
好好坐下聊聊
and have a chat since you came on board.
有什麼需要我改進的嗎  先生
Is there anything I can be doing better, sir?
沒有  你很厲害
No. No. I'm impressed.
你很聰明  也有很好的職業素養
You're very smart. Excellent work ethic.
但更重要的是  你的洞察力很強
But more importantly, you're very observant.
資訊就是力量
Information is power.
就是在這間屋子裡  我妻子向世人
It was right here in this room that my wife revealed a great deal
吐露了驚人的訊息  成千上萬的人
of information to a great number of people. Millions of them.
先生  如果你是擔心我所知道的事
Sir, if your concern is my knowledge of any discrepancies,
我向你保證
then let me assure you --
克萊爾和我都很注重隱私
Claire and I are very private people.
我明白你為何會不信任我
I can understand why you might mistrust me.
我也有敏銳的洞察力  就像你  賽斯
I'm also observant, like you, Seth.
但我還是會有盲點
But I still have my blind spots.
我絕不會想到去找馬博利太太
It would have never occurred to me to reach out to Mrs. Marbury.
她丈夫去世了  也沒留記錄
Her husband was dead. He kept no records.
但你還是找到了  白紙黑字
And yet there it was, in black and white.
我很感謝你把它交給我們
I respect the fact that you brought it to us.
這也是我們為什麼會錄用你
That's what got you in the door.
但想要留下  這還不夠
But if you want to stay, I need more.
你到底是什麼居心
What exactly are you up to?
我受僱於雷米·丹頓
I was hired by Remy Danton.
他要我來找你們的把柄
He wants anything damaging that I can find.
-他有日記的備份嗎    -沒有
- Does he have a copy of the journal?   - No copies.
我把原件交給了安德伍德夫人
I gave the original to Mrs. Underwood,
我告訴他  她的話屬實
and I told him that her story checks out.
-你還給了他什麼    -我手上沒別的了
- Did you give him anything else?   - I don't have anything else.
就算有我也不會給他
I wouldn't give it to him if I did.
為什麼你現在才說
Why am I only hearing about this now?
你是美利堅合眾國的副總統
Well, you're the vice president of the United States.
雷米在為雷蒙德·塔斯克賣命
Remy works for Raymond Tusk.
我夾在了兩位極有權勢的人之間
That puts me between two extremely powerful people.
得小心為好
I had to be careful.
雷米肯定答應給你一大筆錢吧
I'm sure that Remy's offering you a great deal of money.
但他只能給錢
But that's all he offers.
我看到你在參議院推動福利改革法案時
When I saw you push entitlement reform through the Senate,
立刻就明白了誰才是白宮最有權力的人
it was clear to me where the real power in the White House is.
我想為你這樣的人效力  不是乘遊艇兜風
I want to work for a man like you, not sail a yacht.
錢我不感興趣
Money doesn't interest me.
你想讓我中止和雷米的接觸嗎
Do you want me to cease contact with Remy?
不  我想讓你找到盲點
No. I want you to find the blind spots.
-他有空嗎    -只有幾分鐘
- Is he free?   - For a few minutes.
-謝謝    -墨西哥城
- Thank you.   - Mexico City,
你會在那裡見到蘇託總統
where you'll meet president Soto.
我們可以在飛機上練習西班牙語
We can practice your Spanish on the plane.
-那是什麼    -弗蘭克送我的
- What is that?   - Frank gave it to me.
-你有時間嗎    -有要緊事嗎
- Do you have a minute?   - Yeah, is it important?
我要見...什麼時間
I have a meeting with... When is it?
他已經在等了
He's already in the waiting room.
紐約大主教
The archbishop of New York.
我只想問今天晚餐要不要帶禮物
I'm just wondering if we should bring a gift to dinner tonight.
反正是家常便飯  可以帶瓶酒
Yeah, well, it's casual. Maybe a bottle of wine?
你和他們很熟
You know them well.
知道他們喜歡什麼酒嗎
Any idea what sort of wine they like?
也不算太熟
Well, not extremely well,
不過我可以問問他們的手下
but I'm friendly with their staff...
-我會去問明白的    -我可以打電話問問
- I'll figure it out.   - I can make a call.
我在和我丈夫說話  不過謝謝你
I'm having a conversation with my husband, but thank you.
-好的  對不起    -我在官邸等你
- OK. I apologize.   - I'll see you at the residence.
七點半
Seven-thirty.
不
No.
現在不要
Not now.
不  請離開
No. Just... Please go.
請出去
Get out. Please.
瑞秋  是我  我...
Rachel, it's me. I, uh...
你應該接我的電話
you should answer when I call.
我不喜歡留言
I don't like leaving messages.
賽斯
Seth?
艾拉  我只有15分鐘吃飯
Ayla, I get 15 minutes to eat,
這還算不忙
on a good day.
馮山德
Xander Feng.
我沒聽過
Means nothing to me.
康納跟我提過和中國的非正式溝通渠道
Connor told me about a back channel with China.
有推測認為是一個叫馮山德的人
There was speculation it was a guy named Xander Feng.
14分52秒
14 minutes, 52 seconds.
他和雷蒙德·塔斯克有生意往來
He's in business with Raymond Tusk.
他們在中國一起經營一家精煉廠
They're working on a refinery in China.
塔斯克與白宮有關聯
Tusk has ties to the White House.
14分37
14 minutes, 37 --
美國最有錢的富翁之一
One of the wealthiest men in America
和一個中國幕後外交官做生意
in business with an off-the-books chinese diplomat?
而他對華盛頓的影響力從未見報
Influence in Washington never been reported?
白宮在能源危機的緊要關頭
The White House pushes rare earth subsidies
推動核能補貼
when the energy crisis spiked?
你到底要問什麼
Do you have a specific question for me?
我想請教副總統對此的看法
I'd like to ask the vice president about this.
有什麼具體要問我的問題
A specific question for me,
而不是要求安排採訪
not an interview request.
副總統認識雷蒙德·塔斯克嗎
Does the vice president know Raymond Tusk?
據我瞭解不認識
Not to my knowledge.
你在隱瞞什麼  賽斯
You're hiding something, Seth.
我沒有隱瞞任何事
I'm not hiding anything.
只是餓得血糖有點低
I'm just a guy with low blood sugar.
加勒特
Garrett?
怎麼了
What is it?
克里斯蒂娜
Christina.
她總來煩我
She won't leave me alone.
好像她過分地想要幫忙
It's like she's trying too hard to be helpful.
我會讓琳達和她談談的
I'll have Linda talk to her.
不止是這個
It's not just that.
我覺得這只是表象
I feel like it's a mask.
我覺得還有別的隱情
I feel like there's something else going on there.
比如說什麼
Like what?
有時我走進辦公室
Sometimes, when I walk into your office
看見她在和你說話
and see her talking to you...
你們倆總一起出差
...and you've been traveling together so much.
天吶  特莉莎
Jesus, Tricia.
不是說你  但她
Oh, not you, her.
我認為她喜歡上你了
I think she's attracted to you.
而且她以前也...
And she does have a history--
真不敢相信我們居然在討論這個
I can't even believe we're having this conversation.
我希望你把她調走
I want you to relocate her.
讓她去別的職位
Find her another position--
不行
Absolutely not.
我知道這似乎有點反應過度
I know it seems overboard--
她是個很好的助理
She's a good aide.
對琳達很有幫助
She's valuable to Linda,
所以她也是政府的人才
which makes her valuable to the administration.
我是你妻子
I'm your wife.
我應該比這些更重要
I should be more valuable than either of them.
-特莉莎    -她明明讓我不舒服
- Tricia.   - I don't understand why you're fighting me on this
-你怎麼還跟我爭    -我們馬上就到弗蘭克家了
- when she bothers me   - we're pulling up to Frank's in two minutes.
真是太美味了  弗萊迪
Really, superb, Freddy.
我可以說
I can honestly say
我這輩子從沒吃過這麼好的肋排
I have never had better ribs in my life.
很高興您喜歡
Well, I'm glad you liked you them.
我在《太陽報》上看到報道
You know, I read the article in the Sun
寫你去弗萊迪的餐館
about how you go to Freddy's.
希望你不介意我接受採訪  弗蘭克
I hope you don't mind me speaking to that reporter, Frank.
完全沒關係
Not at all.
糟了  我忘了我不該這麼叫你
Oh shit, I forgot I'm not supposed to call you that.
就算你想  我也不會讓你叫我"副總統"
I wouldn't let you call me "Vice President" even if you tried.
而且我完全不介意
And I didn't mind at all.
我覺得那篇報道非常好
I thought the article was great.
報道出來以後生意一下興隆了不少
Well, it's been a big bump in business since it came out.
街上排起大隊
I'm talking lines around the block.
現在你不是唯一去那裡的白人了
You're not the only white person to show up there now.
我先走了  明天還要早起呢
Well, I'm gonna call it a night. I got a early start in the morning.
很高興見到你們  總統先生  沃剋夫人
It was a pleasure meeting you, Mr. President. Mrs. Walker.
我們也很高興
A pleasure. Truly.
謝謝  弗萊迪
Thanks, Freddy.
隨時為你效勞
Always.
不  我不用了  謝謝
No. None -- none for me, thanks.
總統先生  一塊派有益心靈
Mr. President, a slice of pie is good for the soul.
-我吃飽了    -吃一塊派沒關係的
- I'm stuffed.   - You can have a slice of pie.
真的不用了  謝謝你  弗蘭克
I'm fine, really, but thank you, Frank.
我要一塊
I'll have some.
我們倆也要
For the two of us, as well.
她又要逼我多跑五英里把它消化掉了
Now she is gonna make me run another five miles to work off this puppy.
你瘋了嗎  我幾乎跟不上你
Are you crazy? I can barely keep up with you.
-你比我快多了    -你們一起跑步嗎
- You're so much faster than me.   - You two run together?
是的  時間很難找  但我們還是擠出時間了
Yes. It's hard to find the time, but somehow we find it.
沒錯  而且只有我和他在一起
We do. And it's something that's just ours, you know?
是啊  只有咱倆  再加八個特情局特工
Yes. Just ours. And about eight Secret Service agents.
你們倆能一起跑步真是太好了
That's so nice that you have that together.
真希望加勒特和我能有更多時間做那樣的事
I wish Garrett and I had more time for things like that.
我們曾一起去上過動感單車課
We did take a spinning class together once.
你們真該看看加勒特在手把上彎著腰的樣子
You should have seen Garrett hunched over the handlebar --
行了
Please.
再來點酒嗎
Would you like some more wine?
好的  謝謝  我看到你送他的沙袋了
I would, thank you. I saw the punching bag you gave him.
這樣吧  我來一塊派吧
You know what? I will have a slice of pie.
請給總統上一塊派
Pie, please. For the president.
謝謝
Thank you.
我從頭到尾讀了一遍  我覺得很好
I read it front to back. I think it's good.
2014軍隊反性侵法案
可能會掀翻天  但也許這正是我們需要的
It'll cause a shit-storm, but maybe that's what we need.
不能在中期選舉間
Not during the midterms.
我看不出有招致批評的風險
I don't see how we take flack.
我們可是想減少強姦啊
We're trying to curtail rape, for godsakes.
當然  一些右翼人士會老調重彈
Sure, some right-wingers will do their usual song and dance--
先別急  我想自己看過再說
Hold off. I want to read it myself first.
我們向副總統承諾我們會找聯署人...
We promised the Vice President we'd have cosponsors...
我知道我們承諾了什麼  我們要拖延
I know what we promised, and we're gonna stall.
-不要把草案洩露出去    -但你知道法案的要點
- Don't disseminate the draft.   - But you know the gist of the bill.
-我不明白為什麼不能    -洛莉
- I don't see why we can't--   - Lorrie.
好吧  那你先看著
All right, I'll leave it with you.
-還有別的事嗎    -不  沒事了
- Anything else?   - No. I think we're good.
好吧  那我走了
All right. Then I'm off.
跟老公的約會之夜  還不如殺了我
Date night with the husband. Slit my wrists, please.
差不多了就回家  好嗎
Go home at some point, OK?
國會大廈明天早上還會在這裡
The Capitol will still be here in the morning.
雷米·丹頓
這可真棒
This is really something.
還沒完工呢
Ways to go yet.
誰贏了這場戰役  北方還是南方
Now, who won this battle? The North or the South?
雙方都傷亡慘重  沒有明顯的贏家
Massive casualties on both sides. No clear winner.
你怎麼會有時間幹這個
How do you find the time?
我零零散散擠出半小時  能讓我放鬆
I carve out a half hour here and there. Helps me relax.
我都忘了什麼叫放鬆了
I've forgotten the meaning of that word.
送你沙袋就是幹這個用的
Well, that's what the punching bag is for.
說的沒錯
It's very true.
一點就行  特莉莎和我過會兒該走了
Just a little. Tricia and I should get going soon.
你這樣的話一個任期都挺不過去  總統先生
You're never gonna make it through this first term, Mr. President.
此話怎講
How do you mean?
這樣可不行  讓壓力漸漸累積
Well, not like this. Letting the stress creep in.
你是要跑馬拉松  而不是衝刺
You need to run the marathon, not the sprint.
你應該學會享受忙裡偷閒
You need to enjoy these little moments of escape.
多倒一點吧
You can pour more than that.
謝謝
Thank you.
-這是聯軍還是叛軍    -聯軍  先生
- This Union or rebel?   - Union, sir.
別再叫"先生""總統先生"  叫名字吧
Enough "Sirs" and "Mr. Presidents." Call me by my name.
我尊重你的職位  不能那麼做
I respect the office too much for that.
私下裡沒關係
When we're in private, it's OK.
今晚  我不必扮演總統的角色
Tonight, I don't have to be president.
我不是有意要介入你們的私生活
I don't mean to get involved in your personal life.
不  是我提起來的
Oh, no. I brought it up.
你真是為了克里斯蒂娜嗎
Is this really about Christina?
或者是別的什麼事的表徵
Or maybe it's just a symptom of something else?
-比如呢    -我不知道
- Like what?   - I don't know.
我幾乎見不到他
I barely see him at all.
他現在很緊張  海外局勢
He's so wound up in everything that's going on overseas,
中期選舉  經濟危機
the elections, the economy.
他當州長的時候  也不容易
When he was governor, it wasn't a cake walk,
但跟現在是不能比了
but it was nothing like this.
你和弗蘭克是怎麼做到的
How do you and Frank do it?
你們看起來那麼親密
You both seem so close.
我們對彼此很坦誠
We're honest with each other.
我們什麼都不會藏著掖著
We don't sweep anything under the rug.
特莉莎  如果這事讓你很困擾  和他談談
Tricia, if it's eating at you, make him talk about it.
白宮不過是一時的  婚姻是一輩子的
The White House is finite. Your marriage is for life.
-早上好    -好
- Good morning.   - Morning.
你不喜歡這道湯嗎
You don't like your soup?
我用不好筷子
I'm not good with chopsticks.
我覺得與昨晚的女伴相比
I think you'll like this soup more than you liked the
這道湯會更合你口味
two companions I sent you last night.
昨晚我太累了
I was tired.
你考慮過我們昨天說的事了嗎
Have you had a chance to think about what we discussed yesterday?
在中國  接到禮物推辭一次是禮貌
In China, it's polite to refuse a gift the first time.
也許我該拒絕你的禮物
Maybe I should refuse yours.
如果不知道你想要什麼  我們沒法送你禮物
We can't offer you a gift if I don't know what you want.
傑斐遜港大橋
The Port Jefferson Bridge.
你在私下溝通時把項目撤下了
You pulled it, during the back-channel.
-我改主意了    -為什麼
- I changed my mind.   - Why?
我有盟友想修建這座橋
I have allies who want the bridge.
沒了橋  他們就會變成敵人
Without it, they become my enemies.
-我已經兩次受審    -腐敗指控
- I've been put on trial twice.   - Corruption charges.
在中國  我這個層次的人都會賄賂該賄賂的人
Everyone in China who works on this level pays who they need to pay.
殺掉該殺的人
And they kill who they need to kill.
總有人莫名消失  斯坦普先生
People disappear all the time, Mr. Stamper.
我也可能消失  你也可能消失
I could disappear. You could disappear.
別再去賭場  我們就給你這座橋
Stop the junkets, and we'll get you the bridge.
先把橋定下來
The bridge comes first.
副總統騙過我
The vice president has lied to me before.
我要看到他誠意的證明  才會停止資金流
I need proof of his commitment. Then the money will stop.
斯坦普先生  請用
Please, Mr. Stamper. Eat.
你接下來要坐很久的航班呢
You have a long flight ahead of you.
如果你覺得你一定要這麼做
If it's what you feel you need to do.
安德伍德夫人  我在這兒工作很愉快
I've had a great experience here, Mrs. Underwood.
但是這個機會我實在沒法錯過
But this is an opportunity I can't pass up.
-我猜錢肯定給得不少    -確實
- I imagine the pay is substantial.   - It is.
但不只是錢的事  在太空探索技術公司有上升空間
But it's not just that. There's room to grow at SpaceX.
如果你決定了  我不會勸你留下來的
Well, if your mind's made up, I won't try and convince you to stay.
說實話  我最初來的時候
The truth is... when I first came on board,
我以為是同時為你和你丈夫工作
I thought it was to work for both you and your husband.
別誤會  為你工作我十分榮幸
Don't get me wrong, it's been an honor working for you,
但我沒想到要和賽斯一起工作
but I didn't foresee having to work with Seth.
-你倆有些不合    -沒錯
- You're not very fond of each other.   - No.
這不是問題  我們都是專業人士
Which is fine. We're professionals.
但我覺得這樣最好
But I think this is for the best.
僱傭出色人才的問題就在於
Well, the problem with hiring great people
每個人都想把他們撬走
is everyone wants to steal them away.
很感激你能這麼善解人意
I appreciate you being so understanding.
-我們會想念你的  康納    -謝謝
- You'll be missed, Connor.      - Thank you.
賽斯  是我  他剛離開了
Seth, it's me. He just left.
和他談談  然後發一篇新聞稿
Talk to him and put out a press release.
儘可能地平穩過渡
Let's make this as smooth as possible.
我感興趣的有兩個機會
It's two opportunities I'm interested in.
弗萊迪燒烤餐館
家族連鎖餐廳  和零售燒烤醬
Family-oriented restaurant chain and a retail barbecue sauce.
具體是什麼內容
What would that look like?
我們給你一筆預付款來購買你的品牌使用權
We give you an upfront payment for the right to use your brand.
不管這兩項投資是否失敗
Either venture fails, or they both do,
那些錢都還是你的
you still get to keep that money.
那是多少錢啊
How much money we talking?
只要你籤合同  9萬5千
95,000 as soon as you sign.
如果買賣成功了  你還會有收益分紅
And then you'd have a share of the profits if we're successful.
分紅怎麼分
What would the shares be?
這樣吧  我草擬一份合同
I'll tell you what. Let me draw up papers.
你好好看一遍  然後給你的律師看一遍
You look them over. You show them to your lawyer.
我沒有律師
I don't have a lawyer.
那你得找一個了
Well, you should get one.
我不想讓你覺得自己被騙了
I don't want you to feel like you're being cheated.
你還有疑慮
You're skeptical.
聽著
Look,
要不是想買排骨
money usually don't come through that door
一般沒人送錢上門
unless it's looking for a plate of ribs.
我們想賣成千上百的肋排
And we want to sell thousands of those plates.
如果加盟店建立起來  將數以百萬計
Millions, if the franchise builds.
《太陽報》的文章讓你名聲大噪
The Sun article put you on the map.
讓我們用弗萊迪燒烤連鎖店撐起這個名聲
Let's fill up that map with Freddy's barbecue joints.
-你在看什麼    -你說什麼
- What are you looking at?      - Excuse me?
刀在廚房裡
The knives are in the kitchen.
你有槍  不用一直盯著我
You have a pistol. You can stop staring.
他來了嗎  丹
Is he in here? Dan!
-你好嗎    -挺好
- How are you?   - Good.
要喝一杯嗎
Care for a drink?
不用了
I'm good.
我們去客廳吧  那裡更舒服
Well, let's, uh, go into the living room. It's more cozy.
這裡就挺好
Uh, I'm just fine where I am.
也行  你先下去吧
Well, all right. Uh, thank you.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
你一定告訴雷蒙德我請你來這兒了吧
I'm sure you've told Raymond that I've asked you here.
哪個雷蒙德
Raymond who?
在我面前你不用裝  丹
Oh, you don't have to pretend, Dan.
馮證實了你的企圖
Feng confirmed what you're up to.
我沒聽過這人
Name doesn't ring a bell.
我有航班記錄
I have flight records.
他的一架飛機多次飛往堪薩斯城
One of his planes to Kansas City on multiple occasions.
我們還要繼續玩下去嗎
Do we really have to play this game?
我來是因為我以為你有什麼好提議
I came here because I thought you might have something to offer.
不如直接切入正題吧
Why don't we just skip to that part.
你一直是個忠誠的捐助人  丹
You've been a loyal contributor, Dan.
你為我們募集資金
You've thrown us fundraisers.
有很多我們握手的照片
There are pictures of you and I shaking hands.
所以無論你這一季度做了什麼
So whatever you've done this quarter
都可以一筆勾銷
can be forgotten.
但你的資金得停止流往錯誤的方向
But I need the money to stop flowing in the wrong direction.
我還在等你的提議
I'm still waiting for the offer.
你是個商人  丹
You're a businessman, Dan,
-我知道利益是你的首要考慮    -沒錯
- so I know your primary concern is profits.   - Well, that's right.
但我現在要給你比金錢更有價值的東西
But I'm offering you something that's far more valuable than money:
直通白宮的關係線
a direct line to the White House.
聽上去太含糊
That sounds vague to me.
我對印第安人事務局有影響力
I have influence over the BIA.
關於聯邦賭博立法
Over federal gambling legislation.
我已經靠捐款買到了這種影響力
The sort of influence that my contributions have already bought.
但我沒有直接參與  你在總統那邊也說不上話
Not with my direct involvement and the president's ear.
你知道我最喜歡錢哪一點嗎
You know what I like about money?
我能把錢摞在桌子上
I can stack it on a table, like this one.
我能用尺子去丈量它
I can measure it with a yardstick.
我能看見它  聞到它的味道
I can see it, smell it,
用它買任何東西
buy things with it.
房子  車子  衣服  實實在在的東西
Houses, cars, clothes. Things that are real.
你得讓我看到更多誠意
You're gonna have to show up with more than beads.
丹  我請你來我家是因為我認為
Dan, I invited you to my home because I thought --
從後門
Through the back door.
你說什麼
Excuse me?
讓我從後門進來  像傭人一樣
Through the back door, like a servant.
特勤局要求所有人都從後門進
The Secret Service makes everyone come in that way.
這是防範措...
It's a precautionary meas--
除非你給我的錢能多過塔斯克
Unless you're gonna offer me more money than Tusk --
而我認為你做不到
and I don't think that you can --
否則我們就沒什麼商量餘地
there's little left for us to talk about.
我現在向你提供機會和
I am offering you an alliance with a man
在賓夕法尼亞大街1600號工作的人結盟
who goes to work every day at 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue.
我從不信任何白人
I don't place my faith in any white man.
尤其是為聯邦政府做事的白人
Especially one that works for the federal government.
我和你一樣  丹
I am just like you, Dan.
我知道白手起家
I know what it means to start from nothing,
殺出一條路的艱辛
to have to fight your way --
你根本不知道我走到今天的艱辛
You know nothing about what it means to be me.
你所謂的白手起家  比我起步的時候要闊綽得多
Your version of nothing was light years ahead of where I started.
我尊重你  丹  我重視你
I respect you, Dan. I take you serious--
等我在乎你的尊重時  我會告訴你的
I'll let you know when I give a fuck about your respect.
郝利戴  送拉尼根出去
Holiday? Show Lanagin out.
我知道後門在哪
I know where the back door is.
弗蘭西斯
Francis?
沒摔壞  我能修好
It's not broken. I can fix it.
別管它了  我一會兒收拾
Leave it. I'll clean up later.
我們去跑步  讓你消消火
Let's go for a run. Burn off some of this steam.
先生
Sir?
我馬上出來
I'll be out in a moment.
我先走  你趕上我
I'll go ahead. You catch up.
你上飛機前為什麼沒聯繫我
Why didn't you reach out, before you got on a plane?
我擔心我們的通訊被監視了
I was afraid our communication might be monitored.
和拉尼根進展如何
Where are we with Lanagin?
沒有進展  你和馮呢
Nowhere. Where are we with Feng?
我們也許有個選擇  但會比較棘手
We might have an option, but it's gonna be tricky.
■
2010年以前  美國選舉法規定任何個人和組織
向政治行動委員會捐款  每次選舉不能超過5000美元
但是這個規定因為美國最高法院的一個判決而改變
2008年美國前第一夫人希拉里作為候選人參加民主黨總統初選
公民聯合組織制作了一個攻擊希拉里的紀錄片打算在電視上播放
但地方法院裁定該紀錄片性質上等同競選廣告
在播出時間和製作費用上違反了選舉法的有關規定
"公民聯合"於是將此事訴諸最高法院
2010年1月  最高法院的9名法官以5比4的投票結果
裁定當時施行的相關選舉法規違憲  根據這個判決
美國的商業公司、工會組織和社會團體向政治行動委員會捐款時
不應該有數額限制  超級政治行動委員會應運而生
■
"Super PAC"是"獨立支出政治活動委員會"的別稱
在美國  候選人參加政治選舉或者一些社會機構
想要對各級政府議會的立法行為進行影響和遊說時
需要成立"政治委員會"來向社會募集資金
而這種獨立的委員會之所以被媒體冠以"超級"的綽號
則是因為個人或機構向這種委員會進行捐款沒有金額上限
在美國這樣一個金錢和政治緊密難分的社會裡
"無上限"的捐款  自然會帶來"超級"的政治影響
"超級委員會"同普通政治行動委員會的不同之處還在於
該機構不能同其所支援的候選人進行溝通
亦不能在政治活動中進行協調
就是說  如果一個"超級委員會"支援某個共和黨候選人
想要在報紙上登廣告替該候選人宣傳拉票
事先不能知會該候選人  而候選人也不能對廣告內容發表意見
■
2012年的共和黨總統初選
是"超級委員會"首次登上全國性的政治舞臺
根據美國聯邦選舉委員會公佈的資料
在2012美國總統大選初選階段
有近四百家"超級委員會"籌集了一億多美元的競選資金
針對2004年美國議會選舉的一項統計結果顯示
90%以上的選舉中都是資金最多的候選人獲勝
毫無疑問  在美國的政治制度中
金錢是一個不可或缺的基本元素
"超級委員會"便是這種金錢政治中最新出場的一支生力軍